You are.
You are this is the story of
a ship. Live
.
Live
. Live.
live
Live.
Live
.
I have left.
Open for.
The Senate jumping on the board
in full marching on. Coming to
what is happening.
On Cox to talk sensibly the transponder
to the council. Chick chick chick chick
just get right.
I tell because most of what I told you
told us all this time a couple into it in
a trance I said Next make the decision
trying to pull it. Off base make Tommy talk
people.
Shut.
Her. Banjo find her.
On the ships or the transport.
Because another thing stop
the doing my. Bit. Right and get
a. Picture target but keep.
Her.
Ten to one they're all Germans
never get the macaronis to tackle
a dangerous job like that no love no money
on the on charge or do anything for
money or anything but that's what it was
there was in the last house on account.
Their warmonger
a Southern temperament. Thanks
Mother and go. There comes the
dawn of a new day flex much of
a surprise approach that I'm comfortable
with because anybody is guys that somebody
sent me a calendar of like
that last Christmas that have
a squadron of Dhoni as the upper right I'm
going to say that's well parts company
will be able to figure out to get things.
Back up inside the stands out
angle of Scientology. Looks like
a couple things here was
a stop. To
get.
The target to what extent. The
template. Shut.
Up.
Shut up to get some of the public's.
Business waves coming much not just.
Let up we got him on the plane
he's got us to mention.
Egyptians. Comes next way consistent.
Stuff.
From the engine I'm sent to this mission
away from the Gulf. And the Gulf spill it
. Shut.
The. Plant the.
Sort of slip inside Egypt now it's up it's
just on ten o'clock. Every one that it's
because it was
a big auction. He built another wonderful
in the hands of the politics I asked him
.
Shall we have it on the desk or shelves
each of the numbers we have he was one of
those but if I get.
It She is
a good get over. It
separates coming on boats or not wandering
into yes and all up against good. With
a good morning south but want to
get in can roast everything all of
a sudden it well be that it was that of
any other when going to leave satisfied
with
a full power trial yes is well founded well
because again from the government that's
going to get
a company on deck I actually now that I've
depended to go on the ships and. Yes I
sign from and.
Want to. Watch trades up.
In Smoke you get I get them both thank you
sir will you I wonder now that it's not
the moment. Now to Mrs Levitt Yes Oh I did
that last week one of the usual full of
complaints why what's wrong when mother
was to bad again and he got all spin on
that old woman's always in trouble if you
ask me I think she enjoys it what's the
matter with the last time I
was a bank so this time it's
a stomach it seems she can't keep anything
down if I know it's not for want to try
and I think you'd be glad to begin to see
again that's putting it mildly said.
Oh darling thought you would never carry
everything under control probably did not
call names and so telegram came. Over.
With
a letter to ask me let's just keep it we
should educate yourself ship it to practice
in the kitchen so I can buy.
Her That's why it's not just
a beautiful tent it was really going
anywhere I can tell you how to speak to Mr
Sterling about Clinton but you can't
imagine you're bench again. You might take
a call on this committee and given them
to them I'm believing it could be the man
of the message you start getting the kids
money crimes took place somebody said you
keep still as a dad how you got under
my wing don't get markets if you have
a man not so much but too busy
with commissioning making
a rush job of prime time and that's enough
Bobby and then my dad he said. Well you
know me well we will make time some. Bobby
Davis emphasis to join you nicely and it
detonated it will both have to get
a bit of money then you come up and say
good night to perform tonight if you'll
quit now and hang about what to do all
about in the morning but we will have
another brick this new confab as many
questions often as you like you'll be good to
your mother to go to bed. You know to
everything you go on if you go. I'm going to
miss promised promise I'll come back
to me or I can have no right. To.
Even while you excite but no doubting you
must be exhausted I have to think I would
not risk instead of those
things not to go leaving with
a camera special I get to.
Already runs the ice I made
a private business out to get to the
required truck long again I had
a sort of feeling this was an occasion but
at times it is back to doing what you
please more than pleased to love the ship
beautiful memos which is totally out of
my right making such
a rush job of the commission you want to
know I like getting things done quickly so
be any reason we're having
a strange time solving it as well to be
prepared for anything he has been known to
worry about and of course
have you tried it it may be
a bit too sweet. Love. Just right not
a bit too sweet. Course
not I never gave you
a thought I've been much too busy that's
what a surprise for them drives and is
a base from Scotland good memory and those
who go to the phone because of that
a bit high expected like that went to the
new address. Dolling out at that age it's
one of
a couple dozen of before I knew about
twenty times might have to do with new as
good as new and what is going to be
awarded to. Me as I thought it was.
No good warning about the look comes
not much with another. Number said.
I'm not sad just sort of. Getting myself
together and mother can especially at
Michigan. That's cause. I'm
a busy or I'm right
a quick you've got to get your commission
down and you're not come on board just
once before you go to see just to get the
ship I know you have to would you like it
or not my cabin is going to make presentable
the chance to go right after the first
class we did think these are picking
up to the show to do no good in
a minute. Here we go. Here we go.
OK the
attack of
looking. At.
The if you don't
think
you.
The touch thank you
the OK
THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU
OK
thank
you you
. Look.
Look I
think you
look look look look look look
look look look look look look look look
look look look look look look look you
think
you got some brandy and ideas
OK
look OK. Look
this is. I.
Thank you. I
I you. You. I
I. I.
I I. Think that you know you have
foundation to kind of do more
than look at the headlines for
a while then don't look too good does it
oh you can't believe anything that the do
with us and she went last year everybody
talked about him and got into making
speeches after all that nothing our
country nothing happened to us dear but
a hell of
a lot happened to other people do you
really think we're going to have another
world like it to me when I believe it when
our see it you ask me you're going to
see it quicker and you back in I don't think
that it could be sustained they expect
to get back into. Domination that's what
that interacts after you mark my word they
haven't got enough to eat in Germany as it
is this is Connect it's not you know the
one that travels in I'm going to come back
from the end in two months ago they said
that was all of stuff but I can't help what
Mrs dockets never says I think we have
far but if we have another war I'll give
up see after all we went through last on
all you went through and you was too young
and innocent to know anything about it
until exists in
a picture but I don't I mean it's no use
pretending you don't like it always be
young and innocent to me when I
date now if you ask me you've got
a hangover from all that being you put away
last night I was be going to and mother
coming I promise don't call that went to
me. Won't it just carry you better come
down as you are will be no yours we've
got to show again how to commissioning
before you got to see me I don't have pains
you will begin to put those bones in
when the right time comes we're in your
own good bye Oh go on watch how did
respond to the hoose moaning and want to
think it was going right where you never
know you ought to be ashamed of yourself
saying such things like that take your
mothers and give them a fish some are
not it comes mother. That's an example
a man of the devil may get the matter with
you know if again talking the way Chad
tell from the he will contain too much
method to get out and see what you want to
get fast. So you can easily pop down to
the kitchen. I might me I won't even be
endangering the only life and I don't
see any reason to stop now yes but that
doesn't happen to bring you on and become
it's must and if you go on blowing things
up in
a tape in five minutes about if you just
don't pay and then stop it you two I gotta
go no I'm not wasting money on daughters
talks. Too much of all to that's what's
down thought isn't it really good to
shield a guy or depend on it when I was
a thinking years anyway that's that spirit
you know by Mother you got to count for
me and don't you want to go knocking each
other from morning to night. Oh knocks
that time must come on. GIRL
The body has.
Got it.
It's coming a present Thanks
number one. In common
a man that age.
You have no right in the
back. You want to lose
a customer the service of the cup and with
us the ships come down commissioning day
to give them its policy until in the ship's
program I promise is easy enough let me
know it's out of the ball
don't know what it is.
And Adams and Blake. And comb was that
small for having the in chief toga
part into Parkinson he works
in of all comers Whalen of
a letter went to I was better when we won
the all comers come in the night in forty
six again and fell into the ditch when you
got to the ship. Well or another ship is
to tell the others what my policy is always
been Reynolds Adams Parkinson what sort
of
a ship do I want to tell him to be. Happy
That's right any fish and chips or direct
happy and efficient ship
a very happy and very efficient
ship. Some of you might think I'm
a bit ambitious wanting both but in my
experience you can't have one without the
other. A ship can't be happy unless
she's efficient you certainly won't be
efficient and she's happy. Now
a program you most of you see in the
commissioning program of the talent published
in Plymouth general others and you will
have noted that this allows the cutter
three weeks. We've all read your papers
and you know that Ribbentrop signed
a non-aggression pact with Stalin yesterday
as I see it that means war next week so
I will give you not three weeks but exactly
three days to get the ship ready to
sail none of us will turn in or
take our clothes off or swing
a hammer for the next three days and nights
for the jobs finished. Then we'll send
it to
a telegram saying the Titans
ready you can stop. You
for bringing the show you six gas masks
you for not in candy store and I join you
in bringing the rum. Her. To her.
Her her.
Her. Her.
What I'm thinking about
your ass might turn out.
You. Love. Peace and
out.
I am speaking to you. In the
cabinet room in Downing Street.
This morning the British ambassador
invented it. And the German government.
Finally. Taking it and
we heard from them by
a book that they were prepared when the
withdrawal of their troops from. A
state of war would you
give credence. To do now.
It newsagent been received. In
that country in this country
at war with. You can you imagine.
What it did to be
a bank holiday for ash. She's
still
a flood. Watch
.
Was out was.
Told was to was
close to it was to the
cars to the lucky few.
You Lautrec you follow the. News the.
Come to. That US
press. Oh the tunnel Oh God alone supposed
of the heavens and was the Nation of the
sea was compassed the waters with bonds
until day and night come to an end he
pleased to receive and by almighty and most
gracious protection the presence of US
last ovens and the feet in which we said
preserve us from the dangers of the sea
and from the violence of the
enemy to maybe a safe God into
a most gracious sovereign lord
King George in his dominions and
a security for such as possible to
seize upon the lawful occasions of the
inhabitants of island may in peace and
quietness of the God and the native town in
safety to enjoy the blessings of the
land the fruits of the neighbors and the
Thankful remembrance of and this is to
praise and go to high the holy name. Through
Jesus Christ our Lord. Do not sing the
cattle on the back of the him caught.
Early you. Were older you can see the
out of all obese all STEPHEN LONG What was
the hour you leave out of.
It was. Late.
Evening.
Kids beneath your beats me why they're not
going to do it all with the Christmas.
Christmas spirit coming and we get something
going out and give them to everybody
else now and I know this is the talk of
goodwill towards all mankind and you
grandly just you know read
a great example not that I'm not sad all
remembering the last of all spending
Christmas in the Red Sea We was coming home
for my all to you the progeny going to
read so you can be auto right soak in the
Persian Gulf was out there two years ago
and it was to ship the fridge when everything
went bad including the language oh
dear certainly sea life in the big ships
we don't do so badly in the small engine
ran off again stuff I'm not startin
anything to damn sight more live in
a big cruise than destroy it stands to
reason that you don't do no such thing
you're
a Marine you are you don't know nothing
about destroyers What's the matter with the
Marines Well I'm afraid I'll have to tell
you where with the Navy base if it wasn't
for the Marines it was and maybe there
wouldn't be no Marines how you can have any
why we're so nice way to talk and
no mistake you the mother of
a cylon the mother in law of
a Marine past the pole whining and
talks that silly was about right. We
wasn't even
a friendly discussion he'd be saying next
to the friendly discussion last night in
the green men why do I be out
twice now. But I give you
a toast the Royal Marines God bless them
and every Christmas to every man jack of
them Rory.
Thank short your home and our
response to your toast in
a fifteen minute and on behalf of my call
which I'm just me proud enery I'll give
you won't destroy it and the tauren in
particular may I shouted never grow less
never will be strong mean all
right. I should like to take the
opportunity of this festive occasion to
drink the health of one and all present and
to thank
a kindly fate for so arranging to ship it
up to come on from boiler clean two days
before Christmas and
a bit of luck which I think any
standard tell you as little short of
a bloody medical chap can you know again
tack you using that where it be the
opposite me cough that's really expressed
it would What's more that's been very not
we naval tradition since times immemorial
I have heard it was but in the R.A.F.
Or Be that as it may I would like to watch
that I consider we're all. Very lucky.
To be all together on this happy
day taken into account the fact as
a war on the whole rest of a lazy nation
happens to be trembling on the edge of
a base there now what did you see only
said then or or don't say begin with you
know it only puts me off. What do
you get in a boat Friedrich for
a mix of both Nothing really it's
just the way you talk what you young
flibbertigibbet stone seem
to realize is that this is
a very important war indeed we're now well
you said and I've listened to the sound
of your own voice. The speech came trying
to stop him I would treat these paltry
interruptions with the contempt they deserve
and go on to propose the health of one
of these very dear to me he is
a creature of many moves and on
and on through. She is to coin
a phrase very often uncertain.
To me. We're going to devote to
we have three for you very much be an idea
of I swear to be true to her word indeed
So if we call it. Ladies and
gentleman H.M.'s talking H.
a Major a star and. If there is
a gentleman the king. Came to me.
With
a mean if it comes to that yes you call
your manhood the interest of the times when
you may tell me don't let me take
a strong grip of the whole show on air
gaffe. Joining us out there even me to
accept if you will and if you would
have had made like to take some of your
brothers are you going to go Doesn't the
key look sweet Alex and I think as if you
know it's the best Christmas I've ever had
he not whispering into the air I mean
you really ought to put the next thing we
want to drink Come on everybody to the
newly Botros and they're going
to deliver that. Speech
and any the beginning of the M.
My book. About half of my fiance and
myself thank you very kindly as flags
a marina so best letting it only right
and proper that you should make
a speech ALEX Oh no honestly I could go
in and out you know use any idea that.
I had to say the biggest most this is
wait come on outside and everybody the
worship related matters is about to grab
the bazaar open that and get it out of
ladies and gentlemen I begin by taking
my husband's advice and wish you go on
a very happy Christmas. I'm sure Elizabeth
and you'll back me up when I say I'm
going to deliver on behalf of all
wretched neighbor wives I will add
a warning to Marie has been I'm wise
enough to decide to join our ranks Yeah
gallery we all wish you every
possible happiness but I think it N.
. If that tell you in advance exactly
where to even. From experience
I can say that the wife of
a profiler to be pretty to begin
with. That is if it has no stability
whatever you can never really
settle down she moved to
a succession of other people's houses
flats and finished room. To grapple with
domestic problems and. We will
deal with the question of pay
that is all together to create. What we
will deal with is the most important
disillusionment of all and that is that
this is right through to that and that is
that whenever she goes there
is always in her life
a permanent an undefeated rival.
Her husband ship whether it be
a battleship or sloop
a submarine or destroy our. First place in
his heart. It comes before wife children
and think. Some of us try to fight this and
get badly mauled in the process others
like myself. Resign themselves to the
inevitable. That is what you will have to my
poor memory that is what we all have to
do if we want any peace of mind to two.
Ladies and gentlemen. I
give you my rifle. It's
extraordinary. That anyone could
be so fond. And so proud of
their most implacable
enemy. This ship. God
bless this ship. And all who say.
It is just. The ship ever so
much. Against me there's it.
Makes one feel sort of lost to me. That
a happy in the body of
this ship. Thank you.
But I could take such things you know
to get out of your eyes I should.
Note I'm not now nor stuck up to take
a look in the famous else OK here come the
bastards back again. That's not good.
But I think you.
Have. Done it as much as you.
We get today. Not someday.
But if you could.
Keep.
Him out of the baby you
know you would. Tell you
it was good I saw. He's
a regular. Fox
loving cat is it the no you not oh it's
a trap the mind. And Soul see you keep
it and it's still going to drop the.
Said shit I'm gonna think of that
monkey now thanks again man this is not
a dumb shill she doesn't want it she
doesn't have to any Does she think you out
anybody bad you get to play did this
all the time we was in Sunday school.
Some people don't know never. Was that you
said you would you ain't got cool B.S.
You miss you changed there is hope Iraq
me you will come from an agreement.
I get so much obliged if you check spices.
I'm not always won't be never missed it
makes the site as. When you got
a few of these are you about it.
Do you pal that affect I still.
Come to. You. With your name.
Cream. Has
a pretty name any. One of
my customers. And one.
I don't read these are special H M ships
or any beginning to contain. My uncle by
marriage is in the Navy he's
one of the strong if you need
a car engine is now Sam. He's
a petty officer we call him The funny
thing we often call just funny names it
begins with being general a
dash cam video. That was
a ship and I'm not supposed to tell you get
him to list you tell me I'm in the same
terms you might say them cheap but that's
what he's called he's only touring. When
it's
a small world and nowhere is. There
on Obamacare each time Mr isn't it.
Is my friend Jerry make rich. How do you
get paid to make an show. Which really.
There's. A.
Funny ass meet like that when it. Sort
of unexpected. That long train away and
people in it. Not to pick on that one
carriage fighters on yeah I feel that way too
that I suppose we're ready
to get a. Yes person or
a family wanting What's it to you. But
I'm wondering at myself Can you guys say
that your own that you go out much she
doesn't mind the not so long that end of it
tonight also met with tomorrow not in the
open ended on shot down see if I said
they six that the end of the can't be Tory
station we don't waste much time do you
and I can't afford to have
a go chill weekend leave not
very long. In the. Morning
. OK We are coming in on
a date oh no how do you want I could
be getting along they exchange back in
a you're not a stranger not a
moment competent would be give me
a fifteen do you say OK about an hour night.
Are you are all of six there on of the
clock Doria station. To die.
To. Some greater force.
Will Rule.
Out your to be ashamed of yourself and
no mistake began and you haven't had
a gallop sniff what time you with can know
nothing of I'm here OK All my stand in
wind and limb you can go to bed told me.
Nothing Well now look good said Seanie
submarines and some fourteen last week make
up the crew to seventy five people in the
last war that I was in the convoy was
stuck in a man with
a clutch and not about what you did in the
last war day yes really. When you push
me mam. MA over to the magic. We
was in the train coming back from
a. Small world and nowhere can any man be
jealous which is how. It was fate of meat
. She. Says stuff.
Coming over.
I
I.
Can still live to forty
three years of study
a nice smile was the. Same Yes. I
.
Enjoy it look at it Cheerio.
Like. It does sound
funny doesn't it you get used to it is one
thing I should never get used to knit
you going away
a long time well it's your own fault
for marrying or say let me ask you for
a job contest in your many age wives always
coming home unexpected and catching you
having tea with the logical I'm the one
the be the lodger if I'm going to be kept
on your feet for
a week at. Seven old days employers
are. You lot being with cash
when you see China is just you being away
and me wondering what's happening to you
but I would like the following
operations as one gives
a case to check another.
Remember this isn't
a funeral Janani moon and forgive is
not the case now and ship's company.
OK. What are you doing it.
But splendid Congratulations. This is my
wife because you'd like. I do to please to
be John show. Coming with one of my shipmates
in his wife just being that it. Was
his big momma and you do and if you'll
be thankful. For it you take your fav my
life and I came up on the other day my
foot slipped on the gangway and I mean
anything and everybody did them but yes I
really didn't commit eat babies when you
can see again Chief Petty
Officer out here on
a marriage to say she's going to live at
their place for the duration as you might
say but we're spending the next few days
in talky and the nights to just begin as
you intend to go on this big keep
him in order my wife rules me with
a lot of really been quite successful so
far as an adult and talk such nonsense I'm
never allowed to have my own way of anything
we want to talk to and I'm not going
to put it to me because I have been so good
by the best thanks very much thanks to
go back to the prince and about.
The time till you leave he said.
About the going to talk even that it was
not that I thought about that time but I
don't want to go on about it at first but
we have to remember that when it's time
to call to the band came back until. Every
day because they were playing the game
and it was make you feel sort of pent up
emotion that was why you were into its
place for turning it was if I wasn't
a good guy to Probably because that
was the very first time I discovered
a couple disagreeable kicked
they still. Went off to
cricket. This topic to add
a few to mates had to
mention in the middle of
a great quest of lunch. Delicious
piece of railway. It has.
Taken this man to. Think
positively Holtzman. To get ninety
three chance of
a show like. That shows what's
about the chances of the last. To
.
Leave sometime feeling as a piece
of a tiny piece if there really is
a man I'd like to meet.
Well I know none of the.
Six just to be and ten just
but the doctor ordered.
The damn thing from
a few doses because. Since the ship
commission. There I may say is what's getting
the Dr. Yes because Spencer medical
treatment resulted in complete action from
the doctor she seems someone give
the doctor doing their job as
a popular doctor and then just
again I want to you do me
a cunt damnedest not to skilled under you
to school the usual trying to imagine
it's us thinking oh my God I don't know
our. Agenda has that talent thanks go see
it's getting off and I've got the
middle lot they stop you should put
a ten on the night I never did he said again
the. Peace be perfect peace with loved
ones the way.
They are right oh yes
nothing wrong wrong running
a temperature anything now I know why the
first time you have. The Labor wants to
commission a few minutes
and I'm sorry it's not
a lot of guard against our
main base because somebody.
Else can. Be limitless.
Live. From. Philadelphia to take care of
the building itself but it never felt like
a kind of like it was fifteen minutes. To
tell one company in
a way. It's
not about the struggle.
Now make up like. Kill
a communication system to love all of that
placards there's. That's the good. China
stuff still coming up the subtle message.
Well I'm going to be.
Giving up. Such stuff.
If you. Look
look. At Egypt cut up with cutting
back on the time line
to come to the past OK.
Let's cut cut cut.
Cut.
Cut
cut.
.
You know you.
Want the timeline to be shot up look
at the rights of the deal and then
a job. That's it will be my sitting
talking when it gets like.
That so it's out I haven't succeeded to the
demand of the photo yet. But you don't
judge. I'm. Not too bad.
So tempted to take me I'm talking. About
all of my own by to about one hundred
twenty miles up not
a stop US president is all ready to talk
about it. With all the guns but he hadn't
got which I need and I expect.
Some of. That finds. The concussed
of it and yes I think it is
the best of the two stood by the gun even
most of the crew were knocked out is that
true. So many of you do see it
a demo and the product thank. You but.
I'm. Done trying to talk just rest.
To get. The kids home
tomorrow at number one yes that they can
say well. I thought of them in Clinton
days out of the plane.
To see.
People I see belittles I just bought a
car that's going to be what they get
a little bump that I'm. Going to get
I'm just sitting down to give me just.
Let.
Me. Come to our operating. I want to
do things I want to say to you. First.
First I want to tell you that I hold
a shot memorial service next Sunday for
our thirty six shipmates who lost their
lives and return thanks to the ocean percept
him safely through with so many of our
company I expect that it is even
now confirming the cross on
a man who claims to us on this. Second
leg. I want to tell you that you all did
pretty well in the trying time we've been
through when I talked to the head so
small ship is a destroyer
but as art is bound to tell
a devastating it's not fatal and I can
understand the tremendous temptation to
think of your own skin first of the ship
in your shipmate second. I suppose in
a way it's gratifying to feel that out of
the ship's company of two hundred forty
four men two hundred forty three have
behaved as I hoped and expected they were.
One man however did not. That man has been
brought before me charged with leaving
his post without
a mission. And he can tell you how serious
an offense of this nature is in time of
war nor how drastic is the punishment that
normally follows you would be surprised
therefore to learn that
I have let him off with
a caution. Or perhaps I should say with
two cautions. One to him and one to me
but in
a way I feel that what happened was my
fault. This man has only been in the Navy
for six months he's only been on the ship
for two months even so I feel in that
time I should be able to make it clear to
him that I did not expect and would not
tolerate such behavior. I feel that I
should be able to get at least that much of
my trade across. But I
think. I will not punish
a man for an action which I must hold
myself largely to blame. But I should like
you all to know that after this there will
be no more caution the next time you run
into trouble and as leader of
a striking force the ship spun to be in for
the most scraps I know but come up May
no one will fail to do his duty to the
very end. Thank you all for making my task
so easy and the taught in the ship
to be so very proud of. The one.
That's coming to. Unfounded then let it.
Be.
OK I've got to close up Nash Now you show
staying on any longer you can't have any
more to drink it's after as was a matter
with him it's a music if you've got
a penny you can have any hand you can.
Well put it in the start then that's when
you step up. No.
To be required anything law because the
communists told you bottle of it tonight I
want to be drunk sing I want
a big truck. I want to be just
one of the one hundred. Six
sides can.
You.
See
a judge. You
.
Well. I will tell you by Frieda don't
overextend yourself never check I think I've
got to go up to the guy
with the mouse I take.
Issue with the camera and expand for you
in that case to make it be much more can
you tell me how to get it shot half again.
This is he said that this time some.
Tests are getting used to come
up with notions and about. That.
Come they could go in there
and get your feet wet.
I want to get about having them out
a mandate that's right and if things do get
bad you can always go to dark it's got
your have to be good and bad before
I do that or I'll still Cheerio.
You could take all your. You know
what you can do with them give me
a Rolls Royce every time you. Take.
One of the king out. I suppose
you think that's old fashioned too well
so if. You could not the king was in the
lowest street in
a flash roadster would you anything about
the road he said before you say it again
there is nothing on land or sea to put
on a conservative British me give me
a team every time you want it all. Looks
like property in New York you know.
He will. Go to.
He'll kill you I suppose what. I was
trying to explain to Mum is we've been in
a convent.
But he got this morning. It has been. The
chief who was just talking about you.
But I thought he looked very attractive
all those clouds of dense black smoke
belching out thank you. I must say I went
one better round about ten o'clock I
thought she was on. Everyone's bucket
picked up in it to bits by the. Pretty bad
show. She wasn't. Things been
a lash up. Well you probably don't
know if you're going to do it on.
The whole the bridge expedition result is
falling back on time and peacetime as you
know there's
a lot of lip pulling between the services
for the soldiers of our brothers in arms
and it's up to us to get them also they
can live to fight again let them see how
much we have Mother way they feel and
don't forget the successive out of the
curation is measured by the smallness of
the military casualties not the Naval War
. So just
a lot of guests and our lives
will be in our hands. Can
weigh up hearing anything
trying to. Play any.
Judge in the getting the kind that you
promise to cut down you can say to take your
champ champagne belong in an economy up to
someone you have to face in the line to
be explained means when you have
a dynamic. Coming up we are getting one
and college town meetings going on.
Off the job is going to.
Be nail Chuck itself.
Might never think of the scrimmages in
the mischance but it's damn good just on
Revolver all they have
a list. Well trying to. Contradict
you now so I feel as if I've been
away from here we've been away quite
a while too. We put it up north or not again
three ago. Becomes of much the same as
yours the last time I saw it. Comes with
another check this month not exactly will
I got along with being in the US
about such a sort of conviction is
a name given to.
Me to knock out I want to make it.
Only getting off easy tonight.
I never thought I'd basically see
a cup of cocoa going to go come on of the.
Books Well you'll have to have some of.
Your getting quite close going to wipe
pics of those the better the sun on them
still can have everything as most of them
like it is their windows and why digest
them have
a chance to thank you for all you've done
for skin Rose name is part of the time
show I have been given a
great for them to get
a diamond you can spot of the things I'd
love to go out even if you've been I just
missed out on any of the two objects but
you'll be wanting to push off again as
soon as possible as you start out
a busy day you can now go back
to the present go by the given
a coming under the guise of thanks very
much goodbye good luck. Just on rape
culture and check the
former above or. Thanks to.
The
soup.
soup
the
sea
.
Good night. After.
I. Think like
a. Waste
of time given each year. And it's now.
Her.
Readiness said not
a lot of. That goddamn land
but I was playing Call of
the let's talk about it.
Never think it was
a war on with you but there is not
just for me. Because I didn't hold
a. Flat calm looks like he's
a gray silk mountain editors to kind of
once and she said to the cleaners not come
to school. Funny I think this is
a little on it.
Now. That it. Has got its name
and he says he took it was
from me and. Mentioned it to.
A.
Lot of pedigree lovely dates be.
Offended by selfish of me is
extreme. I don't believe it's to forget
the war now and again when i'm can
disappear just very clever of you with all
hell breaking loose immediately over the
defenseless heads. I made most tremendous
effort and then it wasn't really told.
They were Tories having
a mock battle just to keep us of news the
most shameful confession shed escapism I
think. Has been about me the. Times
been shining in the country green in
the streets and peaceful. And you
are on leave even if it's added to
a day off tomorrow. That I wonder where we
should all be this time next year. A lot
might happen between this time next year.
They can go to my Don It was
a good honeymoon money last he. Created
He smiled gently and began again. The sun
was shining on the scene shiny in the on
his mind he did it's been
a base to make the billows move and. This
Google gives
a bigger and bigger every night as well
many how some other stuff because you might
say it's practically part.
There goes another month some.
More of them is going to get it again. When
I was there one thing for that the fish
and I not been much of it but what I was
tested it's that Mr Milligan field is
famous as it's made of the gets right down
to the moment we got to the shop this
morning that became of the Chandra's if
we reach the bottle he's all right if
anyone caught tonight was
a. Thank you. And
I wish that she could get a bit. Of
a. Little bit in the
next. Week that's what I
always say that sinks topped
up again never mind. What
he's moved.
Down to the shelter. Makes me sick.
To your condition I honestly
think. You'll be. But I'll tell
you one thing now I knew much more of
this night after night and. You want to.
Try. To understand why one.
When you. Asked. Where.
Duffy was stopped. Thank
you for nothing are.
Now going to. Shut up about this after all
you are nuts that this is what you say
and expects to Pony in it when he comes
back on leave does he think he turned up on
expected. Me How did someone
in the country Martin have
a few hours. Where we were. Now in.
Coming up can you say such
a thank you note I met. One
on study that you make me tired
something. I don't think trying to be
a sense of what about the god night watches
bouts that he said rather look after
their homes then need to look
enough to just come up to.
Understand as you go you chose already
if what you want right you can reignite
a lot about that just detailed as it would
go when you do it not with it before say
but until then they. Become an opportunist
seventy knots God good not all.
That sounds like
a man just told me that mom. I
got my ticket and it's no use pretending
I don't know you know on the net he does
because he was making
a fuss is that. If. You're not
treating He thinks if you
want to get your knotted
out. With absentee in
a minute anyway just to keep it going.
To be.
The
. Right. Word.
Go. To Nogent.
Yes. So. Mother.
This is the photo of the three months
we put into this did not live oh what
a couple we'll begin tonight with what I
know I know there's no need to rub it in
but I'm choked up with this place
well could you cause you to get
a chill you know he's. Not
that cheap in singles but even
a train what do you expect in Nova Scotia
on the brink you say you know. Must be
one bottle of beer somewhere in Scotland
just wonderful but nothing really comes
post anyway. Yeah should be
all that has to go on the
table with my hands in my throat because
the people from. My page twenty one fight
. For me young sister after months of
mucking about in an already see only gets
a letter from
a young sister to come with her because of
cheer up it may be bad news around here
more travel more stuff some thread left
a little Sokoto more woman fell
down in. The carry carry age carry
the baby covered by some families
a boy isn't what you say it
was born in the middle of
a plate. What's the matter.
They all asked when they got killed which
is shocking. Yeah my misses are living
with me now. I wonder
if anybody's telling.
Them got me kids I'm good.
Now and got no kids.
Those are very grounds to fuck funny.
But I was already. I. Just popped
along the savior in the NEWSROOM
well to much as
a postcard but that's cattle over all the
years we've been married I never normally
get
a post right yet. You heard from
Frieda. Yeah is she doing. It
all right. What's mother.
Cat will. She receive
a lemon. You see. It was all
in the ass to get there and.
It got bleached or even. Killed. Both of
them date. Radios or I chain.
She was under the stairs.
So. I thought of it coming
on the telly. Thanks so
much I'm much obliged but much more.
I think I just go day for the. Day.
I'm glad traders are right in.
She's fine with you. We've got
a sound. Congratulations.
To each. And.
She's going to.
Reach
a solution. That. You can get. It
if you get.
We talk about. The right.
To pick up some I was.
Given the life.
She was I think someone did
come to. Think of. Telling me.
She came in. Just about. To pick up. On
a pretty bad enough. To change
a bomb in the pretty. Anybody leaflet.
No way going exams you expect.
To have is going to be.
Next. To get. The ball back.
I think some.
It's not
a given day because we. Could
. Just turn out
to the High Street. Right about
the district I lived on the.
Most and it.
Played little out of some
account but it. Will.
Break.
Down where it. All right
into making the product.
Of all that persistent past seem to make
it tight and. I'll tell you something
sticky between you and I I'm scared stiff
and it's no good pretending I'm not
a fucking idiot I got something I shouldn't
mind this shit about him asking point
to going to need it. Remember
Nelson Yeah when I know him.
A little. Going.
Through.
My own play you should be you know.
A little. Less.
So.
The old guy. But it is not a name change
a chick name it's true maybe you know
rocked my boat so rocked the ship with your
hand in it since I mean the
guy you think you look.
OK when. We were.
Made but isn't nothing to can
run about nine months. From an
announcement. Just
a minute out see. Can't be jockey Mommy
I want to go must go I want to come ask
looking you caught you going fat down
don't think I'm going deaf again. Because
waiting for an answer.
There's no aren't. There Mrs Bates and
John is from the captain everything's all
right and sadly. Thank you.
Don it's from daddy. He was picked
up and taken credit sounder.
In. The way.
There's no need it I'm. Just
going to break it up like
a top stone it's. Just going
to stand he's standing.
Some of the toss up.
I've come to say good bye to the few of
you who are left. We've had so many talks
and this is our last. I've
always tried to crack
a joke or two before
you've all been friendly
a lot of them. But to day. I'm
afraid I've run out of jobs. I don't
suppose any of us feel much like laughing.
The talent has been in one scrap after
another but even when we had men killed
Madonna to survive and brought the old ship
back. Now she lies in fifteen
hundred fathoms. And with her
more than half our shipmates.
If they had to die what
a grand way to go but now they live altogether
with the ship we loved. And they're
in very good company we've lost
it. But they're still with.
The maybe less than half the town in left.
But I feel. That we all take up the
battle with even stronger heart. Each of
us knows twice as much about fighting. And
each of us has twice as good
a reason to fight. You will all be sent
to replace men who have been killed in
other ships. And the next time you're
in action. Remember the target.
I should like to add. That there isn't
one of you. That I wouldn't be proud.
And honored to serve with again. Good bye.
Good luck. And thank you all
from the bottom of my heart.
Like I could I could. Write about. What
I. Write about Rowling's.
Russia about. But about. Those
about. Mr Knox think about. Think about
what. I say about. The Thanks but
sometimes Thank you goodbye.
To the. Things which has.
Played the Starbucks thanks in
the back of my question. Was my
money. But I had it. Right. But it can.
Buy step one watch Thanks buddy.
Thanks backed. By stuff about.
The story of
a ship. But there will always be other
ships but we are an island. Centuries
to see his destiny. There will be
other ships and men to sail and.
It is these men in peace.
So much. Above all
victory. Beyond all. It's
by changing and changing.
They give us their countrymen.
And.
Live.
Live
live. Live
.